I've been working with Tayyab for a little bit
over a year now, and he's helped me grow my
audience over 50,000 new members.
And that's across short form, like TikTok,
Instagram, and Reels, and long form, like my
YouTube channel, which I spend so much time
on.
And I like working with this editor because
he's just simply so amazing.
Of course that editing, that's a given, but
he's better than that because he can really
take in constructive feedback and then implement
that feedback perfectly, oftentimes going above
and beyond the vision that I had in the first
place, because he has a great eye for content
and a great eye for storytelling.
So if you have the opportunity, the chance
to work with this editor, take it.